[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130307pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "RB", ",", "RB", "CC", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 9, "question": "Tell me why you've gone from dog to lion?", "question_tokens": ["Tell", "me", "why", "you", "'ve", "gone", "from", "dog", "to", "lion", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "TO", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 10, "answer": "Well, it's a -- it's a transformation musically, spiritually and mentally.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "'s", "a", "--", "it", "'s", "a", "transformation", "musically", ",", "spiritually", "and", "mentally", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130307pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VB", "POS", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 42, "question": "What else do we know?", "question_tokens": ["What", "else", "do", "we", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 43, "answer": "Well, let's talk about the important fact that we don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "let", "'s", "talk", "about", "the", "important", "fact", "that", "we", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130307pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNPS", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 54, "question": "How significant is this and what is the thinking, do you think, behind doing it this way?", "question_tokens": ["How", "significant", "is", "this", "and", "what", "is", "the", "thinking", ",", "do", "you", "think", ",", "behind", "doing", "it", "this", "way", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "DT", "CC", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "VBG", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "IN", "VBG", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 55, "answer": "Well, it's a significant coup for the Americans here.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "'s", "a", "significant", "coup", "for", "the", "Americans", "here", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130307pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 67, "question": "What do you think of the operation itself?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "of", "the", "operation", "itself", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 68, "answer": "Oh, I think it was well done.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "I", "think", "it", "was", "well", "done", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130307pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 76, "question": "On the face of it, not that strong, but as Bob says, are we likely to get more meat on the bone later, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["On", "the", "face", "of", "it", ",", "not", "that", "strong", ",", "but", "as", "Bob", "says", ",", "are", "we", "likely", "to", "get", "more", "meat", "on", "the", "bone", "later", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "RB", "IN", "JJ", ",", "CC", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "TO", "VB", "JJR", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "JJ", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 77, "answer": "I sure hope so.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "sure", "hope", "so", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130307pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", ",", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 84, "question": "How do you feel about the fact that this guy is going to be arraigned in a U.S. court in New York a few blocks from ground zero?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "feel", "about", "the", "fact", "that", "this", "guy", "is", "going", "to", "be", "arraigned", "in", "a", "U.S.", "court", "in", "New", "York", "a", "few", "blocks", "from", "ground", "zero", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 85, "answer": "Well, the family is very happy that he's been caught, and 3,000 people were murdered that day and finally we were starting to catch some of the terrorists.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "the", "family", "is", "very", "happy", "that", "he", "'s", "been", "caught", ",", "and", "3,000", "people", "were", "murdered", "that", "day", "and", "finally", "we", "were", "starting", "to", "catch", "some", "of", "the", "terrorists", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["U.S.", "New York"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130307pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 104, "question": "I mean, could this decision get overturned?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "could", "this", "decision", "get", "overturned", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "MD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 105, "answer": "I think that's unlikely.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "that", "'s", "unlikely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130307pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ":", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "JJS", "."], "qSentId": 145, "question": "Is there an argument to say that if this man was taken to Guantanamo, they would get more out of him?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "there", "an", "argument", "to", "say", "that", "if", "this", "man", "was", "taken", "to", "Guantanamo", ",", "they", "would", "get", "more", "out", "of", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "VBN", "TO", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RBR", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 146, "answer": "I don't think -- look, I think we've got to be honest.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "think", "--", "look", ",", "I", "think", "we", "'ve", "got", "to", "be", "honest", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Guantanamo"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130307pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 151, "question": "If you were in the CIA, involved in this operation, would you want him at Guantanamo or in the way that it's being handled?", "question_tokens": ["If", "you", "were", "in", "the", "CIA", ",", "involved", "in", "this", "operation", ",", "would", "you", "want", "him", "at", "Guantanamo", "or", "in", "the", "way", "that", "it", "'s", "being", "handled", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NNP", ",", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 152, "answer": "The way it's being handled.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "way", "it", "'s", "being", "handled", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["CIA"], "LOCATION": ["Guantanamo"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130307pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 166, "question": "Are you alarmed by this?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "alarmed", "by", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 167, "answer": "Totally offended.", "answer_tokens": ["Totally", "offended", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130307pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 187, "question": "But a knife, why would anybody need a knife during a flight?", "question_tokens": ["But", "a", "knife", ",", "why", "would", "anybody", "need", "a", "knife", "during", "a", "flight", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "NN", ",", "WRB", "MD", "VB", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 188, "answer": "You're headed for another tragedy again.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "'re", "headed", "for", "another", "tragedy", "again", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130307pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 199, "question": "What did you make of it?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "you", "make", "of", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 200, "answer": "Well, I think it's good to have this debate.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "it", "'s", "good", "to", "have", "this", "debate", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130307pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "POS", "NN", ",", "DT", "JJ", "VBZ", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 235, "question": "If that is the case, where would blame lie here?", "question_tokens": ["If", "that", "is", "the", "case", ",", "where", "would", "blame", "lie", "here", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "WRB", "MD", "VB", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 236, "answer": "Well, I hate to even talk about blame at this time, as I know the family's hurting, the sanctuary is hurting.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "hate", "to", "even", "talk", "about", "blame", "at", "this", "time", ",", "as", "I", "know", "the", "family", "'s", "hurting", ",", "the", "sanctuary", "is", "hurting", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Global Federation of Animal Sanctuaries"]}, "docId": "130307pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP$", "RBS", "JJ", "CC", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "NNPS", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBD", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 257, "question": "Is that right?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 258, "answer": "Well, I think -- I think any adult felid is at their most dangerous and our standards at from the Global Federation of Animal Sanctuaries call for no human contact with these felids unprotected, period.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "--", "I", "think", "any", "adult", "felid", "is", "at", "their", "most", "dangerous", "and", "our", "standards", "at", "from", "the", "Global", "Federation", "of", "Animal", "Sanctuaries", "call", "for", "no", "human", "contact", "with", "these", "felids", "unprotected", ",", "period", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130307pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "NN", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 294, "question": "How do you feel about the fact that Cous Cous has also been shot and killed as a result of this?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "feel", "about", "the", "fact", "that", "Cous", "Cous", "has", "also", "been", "shot", "and", "killed", "as", "a", "result", "of", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "JJ", "CC", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 295, "answer": "Well, whenever people are allowing direct contact with these animals, they're not only putting themselves at risk, any other people at risk, they're putting the animal at risk, as we see -- we see clearly here.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "whenever", "people", "are", "allowing", "direct", "contact", "with", "these", "animals", ",", "they", "'re", "not", "only", "putting", "themselves", "at", "risk", ",", "any", "other", "people", "at", "risk", ",", "they", "'re", "putting", "the", "animal", "at", "risk", ",", "as", "we", "see", "--", "we", "see", "clearly", "here", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130307pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 322, "question": "How are you?", "question_tokens": ["How", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 323, "answer": "Hey, the pleasure is all mine.", "answer_tokens": ["Hey", ",", "the", "pleasure", "is", "all", "mine", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130307pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "RB", ",", "RB", ",", "CC", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 326, "question": "Now tell me why you've gone from Dogg to Lion?", "question_tokens": ["Now", "tell", "me", "why", "you", "'ve", "gone", "from", "Dogg", "to", "Lion", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBP", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "TO", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 327, "answer": "Well, it's a transformation musically, spiritually, and mentally.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "'s", "a", "transformation", "musically", ",", "spiritually", ",", "and", "mentally", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130307pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", "NNS", ",", "RB", ",", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "WP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "WRB", "TO", "VB", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "WP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VB", "NN", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 357, "question": "Have you been that other person?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "been", "that", "other", "person", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 358, "answer": "Oh yes, definitely, because that's what comes with the territory, especially when you don't know how to handle money, and you don't know what to do with the money, and you let money become, you know, the direction of your life.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", "yes", ",", "definitely", ",", "because", "that", "'s", "what", "comes", "with", "the", "territory", ",", "especially", "when", "you", "do", "n't", "know", "how", "to", "handle", "money", ",", "and", "you", "do", "n't", "know", "what", "to", "do", "with", "the", "money", ",", "and", "you", "let", "money", "become", ",", "you", "know", ",", "the", "direction", "of", "your", "life", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130307pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 362, "question": "And what are the best possible ways of resolving it?", "question_tokens": ["And", "what", "are", "the", "best", "possible", "ways", "of", "resolving", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBP", "DT", "JJS", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 363, "answer": "It's miscommunication somewhere.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "miscommunication", "somewhere", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERCENT": ["95 percent"]}, "docId": "130307pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "CD", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 373, "question": "And what's the best way of tackling that?", "question_tokens": ["And", "what", "'s", "the", "best", "way", "of", "tackling", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 374, "answer": "I think that's 95 percent of the problem.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "that", "'s", "95", "percent", "of", "the", "problem", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Snoop"]}, "docId": "130307pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 383, "question": "Does anybody actually call you Calvin anymore?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "anybody", "actually", "call", "you", "Calvin", "anymore", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "NN", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "NNP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 384, "answer": "No, I mean, you know, because I have become Snoop.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "you", "know", ",", "because", "I", "have", "become", "Snoop", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Calvin"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130307pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "NN", "IN", ",", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "CC", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 385, "question": "Must be somebody?", "question_tokens": ["Must", "be", "somebody", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 386, "answer": "Probably the people I went to school with, some of the officials, and some of the law enforcement that have seen my life drastically change in the appropriate way.", "answer_tokens": ["Probably", "the", "people", "I", "went", "to", "school", "with", ",", "some", "of", "the", "officials", ",", "and", "some", "of", "the", "law", "enforcement", "that", "have", "seen", "my", "life", "drastically", "change", "in", "the", "appropriate", "way", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130307pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBD", "VBG", "PRP", ",", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 393, "question": "When you look back on how you did that and how you broke free from the gangs and everything else, and from poverty, what do you think were the key determinators in enabling you to do that?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "look", "back", "on", "how", "you", "did", "that", "and", "how", "you", "broke", "free", "from", "the", "gangs", "and", "everything", "else", ",", "and", "from", "poverty", ",", "what", "do", "you", "think", "were", "the", "key", "determinators", "in", "enabling", "you", "to", "do", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "CC", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "NN", "RB", ",", "CC", "IN", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "VBG", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 394, "answer": "One of the keys was separating myself, closing the gap.", "answer_tokens": ["One", "of", "the", "keys", "was", "separating", "myself", ",", "closing", "the", "gap", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130307pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 405, "question": "That takes supreme self discipline and dedication, doesn't it?", "question_tokens": ["That", "takes", "supreme", "self", "discipline", "and", "dedication", ",", "does", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "NN", "NN", "NN", "CC", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 406, "answer": "Yes, sir.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "sir", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Calvin Broaddus"]}, "docId": "130307pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "NN", "NN", "DT", "NN", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 421, "question": "My life is in stages, you know what I mean?", "question_tokens": ["My", "life", "is", "in", "stages", ",", "you", "know", "what", "I", "mean", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 422, "answer": "We the jury in the above entitled action find the defendant, Calvin Broaddus, not guilty of the crime of murder in the first degree.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "the", "jury", "in", "the", "above", "entitled", "action", "find", "the", "defendant", ",", "Calvin", "Broaddus", ",", "not", "guilty", "of", "the", "crime", "of", "murder", "in", "the", "first", "degree", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130307pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 433, "question": "Do you feel lucky to be alive when you look back over everything you came through?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "feel", "lucky", "to", "be", "alive", "when", "you", "look", "back", "over", "everything", "you", "came", "through", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 434, "answer": "I feel very lucky and blessed at the same time, because I have seen a lot of people not make it.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "feel", "very", "lucky", "and", "blessed", "at", "the", "same", "time", ",", "because", "I", "have", "seen", "a", "lot", "of", "people", "not", "make", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130307pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "NNPS", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "CD", "IN", "DT", "RBS", "RB", "VBN", "NNS", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 459, "question": "Why do so many people, do you think, associate the gun with some form of self-esteem?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "do", "so", "many", "people", ",", "do", "you", "think", ",", "associate", "the", "gun", "with", "some", "form", "of", "self-esteem", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 460, "answer": "Well, first of all, we are guilty as Americans of promoting the gun as one of the most highly touted things you could have in your life.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "first", "of", "all", ",", "we", "are", "guilty", "as", "Americans", "of", "promoting", "the", "gun", "as", "one", "of", "the", "most", "highly", "touted", "things", "you", "could", "have", "in", "your", "life", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130307pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 471, "question": "What do you think of the debate?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "of", "the", "debate", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 472, "answer": "I don't think we should get rid of guns.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "think", "we", "should", "get", "rid", "of", "guns", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130307pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBN", "CC", "VBN", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "PRP", "VBG", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "IN", "VBN", "TO", "RB", "VBG", "PRP", "CC", "VBG", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 529, "question": "Do you have any concerns about them entering the tawdry world of show business?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "have", "any", "concerns", "about", "them", "entering", "the", "tawdry", "world", "of", "show", "business", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 530, "answer": "No, not really, because I feel like they've been spooned and groomed by being around me and me giving them the uncut version, as opposed to just hiding it and keeping it away from them.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "not", "really", ",", "because", "I", "feel", "like", "they", "'ve", "been", "spooned", "and", "groomed", "by", "being", "around", "me", "and", "me", "giving", "them", "the", "uncut", "version", ",", "as", "opposed", "to", "just", "hiding", "it", "and", "keeping", "it", "away", "from", "them", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130307pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "VBD", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 533, "question": "How have you learned to deal with what fame is about?", "question_tokens": ["How", "have", "you", "learned", "to", "deal", "with", "what", "fame", "is", "about", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "IN", "WP", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 534, "answer": "Definitely, fame is definitely a lethal drug.", "answer_tokens": ["Definitely", ",", "fame", "is", "definitely", "a", "lethal", "drug", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130307pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "JJR", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 542, "question": "Do you take a lot of it?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "take", "a", "lot", "of", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 543, "answer": "I think some people have more tolerance for smoking pot than others.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "some", "people", "have", "more", "tolerance", "for", "smoking", "pot", "than", "others", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130307pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJR", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 579, "question": "Is it beyond that point now?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "beyond", "that", "point", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 580, "answer": "Yes, it's more medical than anything.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "it", "'s", "more", "medical", "than", "anything", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130307pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ",", "IN", "VBN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "NN", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 586, "question": "How do you think he's done?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "think", "he", "'s", "done", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 587, "answer": "Man, that made me feel, you know, like anything can happen in this world, if you put your mind to it and you work hard.", "answer_tokens": ["Man", ",", "that", "made", "me", "feel", ",", "you", "know", ",", "like", "anything", "can", "happen", "in", "this", "world", ",", "if", "you", "put", "your", "mind", "to", "it", "and", "you", "work", "hard", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130307pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 596, "question": "Finally, how hard do I have to work and how much money do I have to earn to be able to afford a necklace like your lion necklace?", "question_tokens": ["Finally", ",", "how", "hard", "do", "I", "have", "to", "work", "and", "how", "much", "money", "do", "I", "have", "to", "earn", "to", "be", "able", "to", "afford", "a", "necklace", "like", "your", "lion", "necklace", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "CC", "WRB", "JJ", "NN", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 597, "answer": "You my partner.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "my", "partner", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130307pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 600, "question": "I think that's the right phrase, right?", "question_tokens": ["I", "think", "that", "'s", "the", "right", "phrase", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 601, "answer": "Yes, sir.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "sir", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]